Canyon Cinema Records, ca. 1961-2009 M1681
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2. Filmmakers
  - Viera, Dave (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Vigil, Carmen (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Von Praunheim, Rosa (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Vosu, Vivian (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Wagner, Nancy (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Wallace, Marian (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Wardwell, Judith (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Warren, David (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Watussi Enterprises (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Wees, Bill (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Wegge, Stig (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Weinbren, Grahame & Roberta Friedman (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Weiner, Peter (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Weisburd, Harry (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Weiss, Betsy (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Weiss, Ruth (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Weiss, Ruth (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Westerlund, Steve (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - White, David (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - White, Margaret (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - White, Neal (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - White, Ted (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - Whiteside, Tom (Box 78, Folder 23)
  - Wiedemann, Dawn (Box 78, Folder 24)
  - Wiese, Michael K. (Box 78, Folder 25)
  - Williams, Lloyd (Box 78, Folder 26)
  - Wills, Sheri (Box 78, Folder 27)
  - Woll, Susan (Box 78, Folder 28)
  - Wong, Al (Box 78, Folder 29)
  - Wuyts, Herman (Box 78, Folder 30)
  - Yang, Minsu (Box 78, Folder 31)
  - Yoffe, Donald (Box 78, Folder 32)
  - Young, Conrad (Box 78, Folder 33)
  - Zalisk, Robert & Eileen (Box 78, Folder 34)
  - Zerox Dreamflesh (Box 78, Folder 35)
  - Zibell, Robert (Box 78, Folder 36)
  - Zoates, Toby (Box 78, Folder 37)
  - Zuckerman, Michael (Box 78, Folder 38)
  - Wiley, William T. (Box 78, Folder 39)
  - Baillie, Bruce (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Lipton, Lenny (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Kren, Kurt: No Film (Flat-box 83, Folder 1)
    contains artist's monograph "No Film?" signed and anotated by the artist
- Series 3. Administrative Records
  - Publication Production
    - Catalog Production Records: 1992-1999 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Catalog Production Records: 1985-1997, 1995-1997 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Catalog Production Records, 1999 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Canyon Cinemanews Production Materials (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Newsletter Production Materials: 1985-1986 (Box 44, Folder 5)
      Includes correspondence and unopublished manuscripts
    - Catalog 8 Production Records, 1999 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Catalog Accounting: 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Canyon Cinemanews Production Materials: 1966 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Production Materials: Catalog 5 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Production Elements: Catalog 3, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Production Elements: Catalog 3, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Production Elements: Catalog 3 Supplement (Box 46, Folder 3)
      Includes photos and original artwork
    - Production Elements: Catalog 5 Supplement (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Production Elements: Catalog 5 Supplement (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Production Materials and Documentation: Update 1984 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Catalog Production Elements, c. 1974 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Production Elements: Catalog Supplement 1990 (Flat-box 48, Folder 4)
    - Production Elements: Catalog Supplement 1990 (Flat-box 48, Folder 5)
    - Production Elements: Canyon Cinemanews, 1994-1995 (Flat-box 48, Folder 6)
    - Production Elements and Documentation, c. 1975 (Flat-box 48, Folder 7)
    - Logo (Printing Elements) (Flat-box 48, Folder 8)
      Contains photographic negatives
    - Production Elements: Update 1985 (Flat-box 48, Folder 9)
    - Production Elements: Catalog 6, pp. ii-23 (Flat-box 48, Folder 10)
    - Production Elements: Catalog 6, pp. 24-75 (Flat-box 49, Folder 1)
    - Production Elements: Catalog 6, pp. 76-125 (Flat-box 49, Folder 2)
    - Printing Negatives: Catalog 4 (Flat-box 49, Folder 3)
    - Catalog Production Elements, c. 1974 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Catalog Production Elements, c. 1974 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Catalog Production Elements, c. 1974 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Catalog Production Materials, c. 1985 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Callenbach, Ernest: Cinemanews Correspondence (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Cinemanews Inventory, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Misc. Cinemanews Material, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Distribution Catalog Supplement Announcement, 1996 (Box 82, Box 9)
    - Catalog Production Elements (Flat-box 84, Folder 2)
    - Catalog Production Elements (Flat-box 84, Folder 3)
    - Catalog Production Elements (Flat-box 84, Folder 4)
    - Catalog Production Elements: Catalog Update 1985 (Flat-box 84, Folder 5)
    - Catalog Production Elements (Box 82, Folder 14)
    - Catalog Production Elements (Flat-box 86, Folder 1)
    - Catalog Production Elements (Flat-box 85, Folder 2)
    - Catalog Production Elements (Flat-box 85, Folder 3)
    - Catalog Production Elements (Flat-box 85, Folder 4)
    - Catalog Production Elements: Catalog Supplement 4, 1978 (Flat-box 85, Folder 5)
  - Filmmaker Accounting
    - Filmmaker Accounting: March 1967 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Filmmaker Accounting: March-July 1967 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Filmmaker Accounting: July-Dec. 1967 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Filmmaker Accounting: Jan.-July, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Filmmaker Accounting: July, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Filmmaker Accounting: July-Dec., 1969 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Filmmaker Accounting: 1969 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Filmmaker Accounting: 1970 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Filmmaker Accounting: 1970 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Filmmaker Accounting: 1970 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Filmmaker Accounting: Jan-July 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Filmmaker Accounting: Aug-Dec. 1968 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Filmmaker Accounting: Jan-Dec. 1971 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Filmmaker Accounting: Jan-Dec. 1971 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Filmmaker Accounting: Jan-Dec. 1972 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Filmmaker Accounting: Jan-Dec. 1972 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Filmmaker Accounting: Jan-Dec. 1972 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Filmmaker Accounting: 1974 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Filmmaker Accounting: 1974 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Filmmaker Accounting: 1975 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Filmmaker Accounting: 1973 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Filmmaker Accounting: 1973 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Filmmaker Accounting: 1976 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Filmmaker Accounting: 1977 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Filmmaker Accounting: 1977 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Withdrawn Films & Filmmakers
    - Withdrawn Films: 1972-1974 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Withdrawn Films: 1975-1979 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Withdrawn Films: 1980-1982 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Withdrawn Films: 1983-1985 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Withdrawn Films: 1986-1987 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Withdrawn Films: 1986-1987 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Withdrawn Films to Anthology Film Archives, 1987-1991 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Withdrawn Films to Anthology Film Archives, 1987-1991 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Withdrawn Video Members, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Withdrawn Members (Box 91)
    - Withdrawn Films: 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Withdrawn Films: 1990-1991, 1900-1991 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Withdrawn Films: 1990-1991, 1900-1991 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Withdrawn Films: 1992-1993 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Withdrawn Films: 1994-1995 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Withdrawn Films: 1994-1995 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Withdrawn Films: 1996-1997 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Withdrawn Films: 1996-1997 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Withdrawn Films: 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Withdrawn Films: 2000-2001 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Withdrawn Films: 2002-2003 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Withdrawn Films: 2004 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Withdrawn Films: 1972 (Box 81, Folder 9)
      hand-written note on a manila folder
  - Financial Records
    - Payout Recepits: 1972 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Non-Filmmaker Payments: 1970 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Checking Account Register: 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Financial Summaries: 1970-1973 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Bank Statements: 2008 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Financial Reports: 1992-1998 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Financial Reports: 1986-1991 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Financial Reports: 1978-1985 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Financial Records: 1980-1999 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Financial Records: 1966-1999 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Federal Tax Records: 1997-1999 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Video Sales Invoices, 1998 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Checking Account Register: 1971-1972 (Flat-box 86)
    - Financial Records, 1979-1999 (Flat-box 88)
  - Fundraising/Grants
    - NEA Grant: 1999 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - NEA Grant: 1997 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - NEA Grant: 1995 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - NEA Controversy: 1997 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - NEA Controversy: 1997 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Warhol Foundation Grant: 1992 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Warhol Foundation Grant, c. 1989-1991 (Box 78, Folder 40)
    - Cover Letters/Letters of Appeal (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Misc. Fundraising Materials (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - AFI Grant, c. 1994-1995 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Fleischhacker Ofundation Grant, 1996 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - San Francisco Foundation Grant, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - San Francisco Hotel Tax Fund/ Grants for the Arts, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - San Francisco Hotel Tax Fund/ Grants for the Arts, 1999 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - San Francisco Arts Commission, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - San Francisco Arts Commission, 1999 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - California Arts Council, 1993-1994 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - California Arts Council, 1996-1997 (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - California Arts Council, 1985 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Administrative Documents
  - MTS Booking System c.1999 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - California Arts Council Grant: 1999 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Office Photos (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Letters to Foundations: c.1966-1967 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Executive Director Report: 1998 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Executive Director Report: 1999 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Organizational Operations Manual (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Misc. Administrative Records (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Lease Agreements and Correspondence: 1983-2002 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Lease Agreements and Correspondence: 1983-2002 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Filmmaker Questionaires (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Manuals: Office Equipment (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Misc. Correspondence and Clippings c.1973 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors: 1983-1999 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors: 2000-2004 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Print/Tape Sales: 2002 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Rent Subsidy Grants: 2001-2003 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Film Arts Foundation Fiscal Sponsorship (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors General Meeting: 2001 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors: 1996 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors: 1997 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors: 1997 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Board of Directors: 1997 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors: 1993-1994 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors: 1999-2000 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors: 1999-2000 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors: 1991-1999 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors: 1991-1999 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors: 2003 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Misc. Correspondence c.1973-1981 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Filmmaker Correspondence: 1967-1972 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Filmmaker Correspondence: 1967-1982 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Filmmaker Correspondence: 1967-1982 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Filmmaker Correspondence: 1967-1982 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Filmmaker Correspondence: 1990-2002, 1967-1982 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Filmmaker Correspondence: 1990-2002, 1967-1982 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Misc. Correspondence: 1993-1995 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Filmmaker Information Sheets (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Filmmaker Agreements (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Filmmaker Agreements (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Administrative Procedures (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Advertising Research and Production Elements (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Filmmaker Correspondence: 1981-1989 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Resumes (Box 44, Folder 6)
    Includes staff and board resumes and job application materials
  - Articles of Incorporation: 1973 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Articles of Incorporation (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Includes 501(c)3 applications
  - Articles of Incorporation (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Articles of Incorporation (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Canyon Cinemanews Administrative Records 1971-1974 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    Includes photos
  - Canyon Cinemanews Administrative Records: 1966-1971 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    Includes Photographs and orginal artworks
  - Canyon Cinemanews Administrative Records: 1972 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Mike Getz Correspondence: 1972-1973 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: 1970-1971 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Office Stationary (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Press Clippings and Correspondence: 1968-1976 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Misc. Correspondence and Collected Ephemera, c. 2002 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Accounts Ledger, 2000-2007 (Flat-box 51)
    Bound Volume
  - Accounts Ledger, 1975-1985 (Oversize-box 52)
  - Accounts Ledger, 1967-1968 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence: Adelphi Pictures Corp., 1968 (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Ubu Films/ Bruce Conner Dispute, 1971 (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - Press Clippings: 1966-1981 (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - Press Clippings: "Independent Filmmaker" Magazine, 2000 (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence and Clippings: Ubu Films, c. 1968-1969 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence and Clippings: Ubu Films (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Filmmakers' Names Lists (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Canyon Cinema Policy Statement (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Board Election Forms, 1995-1996 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Misc. Office Ephemera (Box 82, Folder 10)
- Series 4. Exhibition Records
  - Canyon Cinematheque Earnings and Expenses: 1968-1972 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Canyon Cinematheque Press Releases and Publicity: 1968-1973 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - 20th Anniversary Exhibition Series, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Canyon Cinematheque Exhibition Calendars: c. 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Canyon Cinematheque Publicity: 1967-68 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Canyon Cinematheque Correspondence: 1972 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Canyon Cinematheque Accounting Sheets, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Canyon Cinematheque Reviews c.1970 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Canyon Cinematheque Advertising Receipts, c. 1971 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Canyon Cinematheque Advertising: 1972 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Canyon Cinematheque Press Clippings (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Canyon Cinematheque: Misc. Receipts (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Canyon Cinematheque Rental Invoices: 1970-1974 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Canyon Cinematheque: Films Shown, c. 1970-1972 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Canyon Cinematheque: Original Handbills (Box 46, Folder 4)
    Contains original artworks
  - Canyon Cinematheque: Fliers and Press Releases (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Canyon Cinematheque: Misc. Notes and Correspondence, c. 1971 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Canyon Cinematheque: Fliers and Press Releases, c. 1972 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Canyon Cinematheque: Correspondence and Collected Ephemera (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Canyon Cinematheque: Films by Women (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Benefit Screenings, 1986-1987 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Total Mobile Home Screenings, 1995-1996 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - SFMOMA screenings (Box 46, Folder 12)
    Contains original slides and photographs
  - Canyon Cinematheque: Correspondence and Collected Ephemera (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Canyon Cinematheque: Press Releases and Publicity, 1972-1974 (Flat-box 48, Folder 3)
  - Exhibition Calendars c. 1965-1988 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    Contains mixed exhibition calendars from Canyon Cinema and San Francisco Cinematheque
  - Exhibition Calendars c. 1965-1988 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Exhibition Calendars c. 1965-1988 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Exhibition Calendars c. 1965-1988 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Exhibition Calendars c. 1965-1988 (Flat-box 49, Folder 4)
  - Canyon Cinema Traveling Cinema, 1977 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Exhibition Calendar, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Exhibition Calendar, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Exhibition Calendar, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Exhibition Calendar, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Exhibition Calendar, c. 1965 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Canyon Cinematheque Admissions Pass, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Exhibition Calendars, c. 1970-1977 (Flat-box 83, Folder 2)
  - Exhibition Calendars, c. 1971-1981 (Flat-box 83, Folder 3)
  - Exhibition Calendars, c. 1972-1981 (Flat-box 83, Folder 4)
  - Exhibition Calendars, c. 1971 (Flat-box 82, Folder 12)
- Series 5. Collected Ephemera (Oversize-box 49, Folder 6)
  - Collected Ephemera: Exhibition Venues
    - Whitney Museum Program Notes and Press Clippings, Dec. 1970-June 1971 (Flat-box 49, Folder 5)
    - Whitney Museum Program Notes, 1971 (Flat-box 49, Folder 7)
    - Filmmakers' Cinematheque (NYC): Program Notes, c. 1966-1969 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Pacific Film Archive (Berkeley): Exhibition Calendars, c. 1975-1978 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Misc. Film Showcases, c. 1978 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Misc. Exhibition Calendars, c. 1979-1982 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Misc. Exhibition Calendars, c. 1979-1982 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Misc. Exhibition Calendars, c. 1979-1983 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Misc. Exhibition Calendars, c. 1979-1983 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Film Center Gazette (Philadelphia), c. 1979 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Film Arts Festival (San Francisco) Program, 2005 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Misc. Exhibition Venues, c. 1996-2000 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Misc. Exhibition Venues, c. 1996-2000 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Misc. Exhibition Venues, c. 1996-2000 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Misc. Exhibition Venues, c. 1996-2000 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Festival Internacional de Cine de Gijon: Festival Program, 1998 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - No Nothing Cinema Poster, 1992 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Clair-Obscur Film Festival (Basel), 1999 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Pop-Off: The Regular 8 Faction--Festival Program, 1998 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Bangkok International Film Festival, 1999 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Misc. Exhibition Venues, 1972-1983 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Misc. Exhibition Venues, 1984-1985 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Chicago Filmmakers, 1984-1985 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Collective for Living Cinema (NYC), 1975-1982 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Film Forum (NYC), c. 1975-1979 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Film Forum/Millennium Film Workshop (NYC), c. 1972-1978 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Museum of Modern Art (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Pacific Film Archive, c. 1975-1979 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Misc. Film Festivals, c. 1967-1970 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Misc. Film Festivals, c. 1967-1970 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Misc. Film Festivals, c. 1967-1970 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Misc. Film Distributors, c. 1973-76 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Misc. Film Distributors, c. 1973-76 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Misc. Film Distributors, c. 1972-1984 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Anthology Film Archives (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Forum BHZ (Brazil) Video 95 Festival Program, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Le Nouveau Festival (Montreal) 1995 Program (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Wellington Film Festival Program, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Misc. Film Exhibitors, c. 1996 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Misc. Film Exhibitors, c. 1990 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Misc. Film Exhibitors, c. 1995 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Misc. Film Exhibitors, c. 1973-1993 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Misc. Film Exhibitors, c. 1973-1993 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Misc. Film Exhibitors, c. 1973-1993 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Misc. Film Exhibitors, c. 1973-1993 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Misc. Film Exhibitors, c. 1983 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Misc. Film Exhibitors, c. 1994-1995 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Misc. Film Exhibitors, c. 1971-2000 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Misc. Film Exhibitors, c. 1971-2000 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Festival Internacional de Cine De Gijon (Spain) 1999 Festival Program (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Festival de Cine Alcala de Henares (Spain) 1998 Festival Program (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Pasadena Film Forum (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Pacific Cinematheque/The Funnel (Vancouver), c. 1976-1985 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Pacific Cinematheque/The Funnel (Vancouver), c. 1976-1985 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Anthology Film Archives Exhibition Calendars, 1999-2000 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - San Francisco Int'l Asian American Film Festival Program, 2000 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Pacific Film Archive (Berkeley), 1988-1989 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Pacific Film Archive (Berkeley), 1990 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Pacific Film Archive (Berkeley), 1995-1999 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - University Film Study Center (Princeton) (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Misc. Film Exhibitors, c. 1986 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Whitney Museum (NYC), c. 1975-1982 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Misc. Film Exhibitors, c. 1976-1996 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Misc. Film Exhibitors, c. 1976-1996 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Misc. Film Exhibitors, c. 1976-1996 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Misc. Film Exhibitors, c. 1976-1996 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Misc. Film Exhibitors, c. 1976-1996 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Chicago Filmmakers, 1984-1986 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Los Angeles Film Forum, c. 1991 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Berks Filmmaers (Reading PA), 1990-1991 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Pacific Cinematheque (Vancouver), 1981-1982 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Artists' Television Access (San Francisco), 1995-1996 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Millennium Film Workshop (NYC), 1988-1996 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Los Angeles Film Forum, 1992 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Chicago Filmmakers, c. 1990-1995 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Chicago Filmmakers, c. 1990-1995 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Pleasuredome (Toronto), c. 1990-1995 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - First Person Cinema (Boulder), c. 1986-1992 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Collective for Living Cinema (NYC), c. 1986-1987 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Anthology Film Archives, c. 1962-1982 (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Misc. Exhibition Venues, c. 1962-1982 (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - Misc. Exhibition Venues, c. 1962-1982 (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Misc. Exhibition Venues, c. 1962-1982 (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - Misc. Exhibition Venues, c. 1962-1982 (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - National Video Festival Program, 1985 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Misc. Exhibition Venues (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Misc. Exhibition Venues (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Film Arts Festival Program, 2005 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Misc. Exhibition Venues (Flat-box 83, Folder 5)
    - Misc. Exhibition Venues (Flat-box 83, Folder 6)
    - Misc. Exhibition Venues (Flat-box 83, Folder 7)
    - Misc. Exhibition Venues, c. 1979-2000 (Flat-box 49, Folder 8)
  - Collected Ephemera Miscellaneous
    - Manuals: Office Equipment (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - James Agee Film Project, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Filmmakers' Travel Sheet, c. 1974-1976 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Film Reviews, c. 1974-1978 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Youngblood, Gene: Misc. Writings, c. 1968 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - SOHO News: Reviews, c. 1976-1978 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Big As Life: An American History of 8mm Films (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Third World Newsreel Film Index, 1983-1984 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Zipporah Films Catalog, 1983 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Release Print Journal, Misc. Issues, 1986-1989 (Box 80, Folder 4)
      "The Magazine of the Film Arts Foundation" (San Francisco)
    - Release Print Journal, Misc. Issues, 1989-1995 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Release Print Journal, Misc. Issues, 1995-1996 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Release Print Journal, Misc. Issues, 1998 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Proximity Canyon News, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 12)
      external publication, possibly edited by Dean Snider
    - Misc. Ephemera (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Cultural News & Services Newsletter, c. 1977 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Flyer: Byron Black Performance (Flat-box 84, Folder 1)
      contains orginal collage
- Series 6. Media
  - Reel to reel films, audio-cassettes, mini-cassettes, VHS tapes. (Carton 92)